kling_faH9
kling_omf
kling2_6
kling3_0H9
kling3_0
kling_faH9
kling2_6H9
kling3_0H9
kling3_0H9
generate
generateKey
generateSubkeys
generateClientKeyExchange
generateServerKeyExchange
protobuf:"varint,20,opt,name=java_generate_equals_and_hash,json=javaGenerateEqualsAndHash" json:"java_generate_equals_and_hash,omitempty"
{{end}}operandSHA-224SHA-256SHA-384SHA-512answersFreeSidSleepEx!!merge!!float (with %d:%s%spopMode existsdefaultepsilonaction_'false'GREATERPERCENTCOMMENTNUM_INTESC_SEQprimaryoptExprproto: AES-CBCeae_prkdkp_prkderived2.5.4.62.5.4.32.5.4.52.5.4.72.5.4.82.5.4.9englishdeutschitalian^[ \t]*ILLEGALGOAMD64,cryptoGOARM64GOPPC64androidfreebsdriscv64illumosloong64ppc64lesparc64openbsdsolarisPackageImportsMethodsamxtileamxint8amxbf16osxsaveavxifmaavxvnniabl1943akuapemalalc97arevelaarevmdaarkaikabalankabauddhabohoricemodengfonnapagrclassgrmistrhepburnitihasalaukikalemosinltg1929ltg2007metelkomonotonpahawh2pahawh3pahawh4polytonprovencsursilvsutsilvvaidika%s-%s%sreadlinktruncatefile+netFullPathgeneratesettingsproductsget <id>workflowset <id>canceledfull-setPriorityPlatform--avatarIndustrystyle_idms_imagelogo-urljob_typevoice-idvoice_iddurationintervaldev-fnf.main-jobcategoryJob TypeRequired
higgsfield.aibrand_context%s (%s, %s)
Fetch a brand kitpublish <game_id>aplus_hero_banneraplus_pain_pointsaplus_ingredientsaplus_endorsementpagination cursorBusiness overview%s requires --%s.max wait durationfnf.higgsfield.aidev.higgsfield.ainano_banana_2_jobuploaded image idFetch failed: %s.Timeout after %s.page size (1-100)goroutine profileAllThreadsSyscallcontainermaxprocsGC assist markingselect (no cases)sync.RWMutex.Lockwait for GC cycletrace proc statussync.(*Cond).Wait: missing method invalid addrBytesinvalid wordBytesnotetsleepg on g0bad TinySizeClassimmortal metadataruntime: pointer g already scannedmark - bad statusscanObject n == 0swept cached spanmarkBits overflowruntime: summary[runtime: level = , p.searchAddr = RtlGetCurrentPeb
invalid nil Durationduplicate map key %v%s: invalid %v valuemissing IPv6 addressunexpected characternegative Prefix bitsunknown PSK identitycertificate requiredcipher_suites kdf_idgzip: invalid headerheader line too longinvalid property: %wgetCert can't be nilinvalid UTF-8 stringx509: malformed spkitransport queue fullX-Sentry-Rate-Limitsflag: help requestedinteger overflow: %qmissing value for %snumber has no digitsbad karatsuba lengthChangeServiceConfigWCheckTokenMembershipQueryServiceConfig2WQueryServiceStatusExRegisterEventSourceWCertFindChainInStoreGetWindowsDirectoryWProcessIdToSessionIdSetVolumeMountPointWRtlInitUnicodeStringEnumProcessModulesExGetModuleFileNameExWGetModuleInformationSetupDiOpenDevRegKeySHGetKnownFolderPathUnloadKeyboardLayoutinvalid map key: %#vunknown scalar styleinvalid parser statewhile parsing a nodewhile scanning a tag,hasSemanticContext=DFA after MatchATN: start state closure=predictATN decision ctx sensitive state fieldInitializerListinvalid field numberinvalid map key typeunsupported KDF %04xinvalid integer typeasn1: syntax error: sentinel error valuesha3: Sum after ReadFetch an ad referenceList available voicesbrand kit id to applygame title (required)game archive is emptyUnknown %s params: %shttps://higgsfield.aidev-fnf.higgsfield.aishow text models onlyHIGGSFIELD_SENTRY_DSNAdjustTokenPrivilegesLookupPrivilegeValueWSetNamedSecurityInfoWNetUserGetLocalGroupsGetProfilesDirectoryWnegative shift amountdataindependenttimingsystem goroutine wait/gc/heap/allocs:bytesruntime: work.nwait=  previous allocCount=, levelBits[level] = runtime: searchIdx = profiler hash bucketsdefer on system stackpanic on system stackasync stack too largestartm: m is spinningstartlockedm: m has pfindRunnable: wrong ppreempt at unknown pcreleasep: invalid argcheckdead: runnable g from outside bubble
Additional Commands:CLAUDE_CODE_ENTRYPOINTinworld_text_to_speechcinematic_studio_imagemarketing_studio_imagetopaz_image_generativehiggsfield-go/%s go/%sOAuth config missing: Missing PKCE verifier.Authorization failed: reflect.Value.MapIndexreflect.MapIter.SetKeyunexpected method stepreflect.Value.SetFloat to array with length __not_strictly_false__cel.validator.durationcontext can not be nilgoogle.protobuf.Structunknown enum name '%s' into Go struct field json: unknown field %qhttp2: frame too largewrite on closed bufferbody closed by handlerapplication/postscriptDEBUG_HTTP2_GOROUTINESMAX_CONCURRENT_STREAMSframe_data_pad_too_bigunexpected empty hpackmalformed HTTP requestmalformed HTTP versionX-Content-Type-OptionsUnsupported Media Typepconn is not in flightinvalid urn prefix: %qZEIT_GITHUB_COMMIT_SHAZEIT_GITLAB_COMMIT_SHAexit hook invoked exitreflectlite.Value.Elem%SystemRoot%\system32\flag %q does not existfailed to parse IP: %qvalue %s is not a timeundefined variable: %sindex out of range: %dInscriptional_ParthianNyiakeng_Puachue_Hmongvalue is a nil pointerunsupported style '%s'CloseCurlyDoubleQuote;DoubleContourIntegral;FilledVerySmallSquare;NegativeVeryThinSpace;NotPrecedesSlantEqual;NotRightTriangleEqual;NotSucceedsSlantEqual;.localhost.localdomainmissing ']' in addressinvalid address familyoperation was cancelederror parsing regexp: COMPONENT_TYPE_CHECKERunexpected %s type: %vinvalid validator: nilinvalid extension: niltrue && true   // trueerror || error // trueadd_duration_timestampadd_timestamp_durationnegate a numeric value// error is generated.'cat' < 'cab' // false2 in [1, 2, 3] // truebool('false') // falsedouble('1.23') // 1.23string(true) // 'true'string(-123) // '-123'timestamp_to_timestampid: %v, attributes: %vno such overload: %s()unsupported ident kindunsupported syntax '?'invalid double literalunsupported expressionjava_string_check_utf8php_metadata_namespaceinvalid empty type URLunknown parent type %TFIELD_PRESENCE_UNKNOWNIPv4 address too shortmultiple :: in addressbad bits after slash: error decoding messageinappropriate fallbackECDSAWithP256AndSHA256ECDSAWithP384AndSHA384ECDSAWithP521AndSHA512extended master secrethkdf: counter overflowunexpected length codegzip: invalid checksumaccess-control-max-ageinvalid HTTP header %sinvalid Trailer key %qhpack: string too longheader field %q = %q%sidna: invalid label %qx509: malformed issuerbuild line missing '='pkg/tool/windows_amd64wrong number of fieldsunexpected right parenexpected end; found %sparenthesized pipelineInt.Scan: invalid verbinvalid number base %dinternal inconsistencyskipping Question Nameskipping Question TypeEnumDependentServicesWCancelMibChangeNotify2WaitForMultipleObjectsNtSetSystemInformationRtlDeleteFunctionTableRtlGetNtVersionNumbersSetupDiEnumDriverInfoWSetupDiGetClassDevsExWWSALookupServiceBeginWInvalid ATNConfig typeDFA after predictATN: oneof type already setbytes,1002,opt,name=goSTRIP_ENUM_PREFIX_KEEPoverflowing coordinatezero length BIT STRINGsimulated CAST failuresha3: Write after ReadXXX_InternalExtensionsinvalid UTF-8 detected0123456789abcdefABCDEFcrypto/rsa: p * q != nMarketing Studio assetsGenerate a DTC ad imageCreate a generation jobShow one generation jobList uploaded media IDsuploaded video input idFlag --url is required.ad format id (required)%s should be %s, got %sAnalysis: not availableextra brand description%s ended with status %quse one or more --image  higgsfield auth loginSelected workspace: %s
/apps/virality-predictorfnf-api-gw.higgsfield.aivisual style constraintsjob ended with status %quse --image <path-or-id>size(params.medias) == 1size(params.medias) >= 1search by name or promptproduct title (required)print raw JSON responseslist Soul 2.0 referencestracecheckstackownershipwaiting for cgo callbackhash of unhashable type span has no free objectsruntime: found obj at *(runtime: VirtualFree of /cgo/go-to-c-calls:calls/gc/heap/objects:objects/sched/latencies:secondsqueuefinalizer during GCcheckfinalizers: queue: update during transitionruntime: markroot index can't scan our own stackgcDrainN phase incorrectpageAlloc: out of memoryruntime: p.searchAddr = range partially overlaps [recovered, repanicked]stack trace unavailable
Additional help topics:' does not support flag 'ShellCompDirectiveNoSpaceShellCompDirectiveDefaulthttps://fnf.higgsfield.aierror reading 'usage': %werror marshaling '%s': %werror reading 'fonts': %wInvalid credentials file.reflect.Value.SetMapIndexreflect: Bits of nil Typereflect.StructOf: field "reflect.Value.OverflowInttimestamp_to_day_of_monthtimestamp_to_millisecondsunsigned integer overflowgoogle.protobuf.Timestampgoogle.protobuf.BoolValuegoogle.protobuf.ListValuegoogle.protobuf.NullValuetype conversion error: %vjson: Unexpected key typejson: unsupported value: not at beginning of valuenet/url: invalid userinfohttp: invalid cookie nametext/plain; charset=utf-8connection is unavailablehttp: invalid Cookie.Namehttp2: Framer %p: read %vframe_data_pad_byte_shortframe_settings_has_streamframe_headers_zero_streamframe_headers_pad_too_bigframe_priority_bad_lengthhttp2: invalid header: %vhttp2: unsupported schemeread_frame_unexpected_eof{...} wildcard not at endhttp: invalid Host headerHTTP/1.1 100 Continue
cipher: incorrect length IVunsupported public key typemismatching message lengthsinvalid Message.Mutable on invalid P224 point encodinginvalid P256 point encodinginvalid P384 point encodinginvalid P521 point encodinginput overflows the modulusextendedGCD: a or m is zeroNAF digits must fit in int8os: process already finishedos: process already releasedGetFileInformationByHandleExCreate a workflow generationPoll a job until it finishesClear the selected workspacebatch size 1..20 (default 1)block until the job finishesdev-fnf-api-gw.higgsfield.aimarketplace product categoryUnknown reference_source %q.use --end-image <path-or-id>block until import completeshiggsfield %s (%s) built %s
%sNon-Authoritative InformationProxy Authentication RequiredUnavailable For Legal Reasonsdup idle pconn %p in freelistapplication/x-sentry-envelopeexec: Wait was already calledreflect: Out of non-func typenil data; no entry for key %qcannot 3-index slice a stringmismatched local address typeinvalid character class rangeunsupported constant kind: %v%d more errors were truncatedinvalid feature: missing nameunsupported yaml for TypeDescargument is not an identifierjava_generate_equals_and_hashBUG: internal error (unknown)descriptor mismatch: %v != %vfile %q is already registered%v: assigning invalid type %T2006-01-02T15:04:05.000000000unknown certificate authoritytls: too many ignored recordstls: invalid outer extensionstls: invalid NextProtos valuetls: invalid server key sharetls: invalid client key sharetls: unsupported key exchangetls: invalid session encodingtls: unknown session encodingmime: invalid media parameteraccess-control-expose-headersaccess-control-request-methodx509: cannot parse dnsName %qx509: unsupported time formatx509: cannot parse URI %q: %sx509: malformed serial numbermax expression depth exceededCM_Get_Device_Interface_ListWRegisterServiceCtrlHandlerExWGetNumberOfConsoleInputEventsGetSystemPreferredUILanguagesGetThreadPreferredUILanguagesSetupDiCancelDriverInfoSearchSetupDiGetClassInstallParamsWSetupDiSetClassInstallParamsWalias value must not be emptywhile parsing a block mappingwhile parsing a flow sequenceunexpected low surrogate areacannot decode %s `%s` as a %swhile increasing indent leveldid not find the expected '>'did not find expected tag URIwhile scanning a block scalarwhile parsing a quoted scalarwhile scanning a plain scalarsemanticContext cannot be niltoken recognition error at: ', resolvesToJustOneViableAlt=non-contiguous repeated fieldSTRIP_ENUM_PREFIX_UNSPECIFIEDsyntax error (line %d:%d): %vcrypto/aes: invalid key size crypto/des: invalid key size crypto/rc4: invalid key size invalid encapsulated key sizeinteger not minimally-encodedzero length OBJECT IDENTIFIER20060102150405.999999999Z0700FIPS 140-3 self-test failed: FIPS 140-3 self-test passed: mismatching extension lengthsinvalid type: got %v, want %vinvalid input for enum %v: %sinvalid value for enum %v: %s%T does not implement Marshalfield %v has invalid type: %vinvalid P256 element encodingcrypto/rsa: |p - q| too smallos: process handle unavailableruntime.AddCleanup: ptr is nilPrint the current access token
1)Failed to upload media bytes: %s: %sRun: %s workspace set <workspace_id>Failed to clear workspace selection.https://fnf-api-gw.higgsfield.ai/fnflfstack node allocated from the heap) is larger than maximum page size (objects with pointers must be zeroedruntime: invalid typeBitsBulkBarrieruncaching span but s.allocCount == 0Scan trace for cleanup/finalizer on /memory/classes/metadata/other:bytes/sched/goroutines/running:goroutines/sched/goroutines/waiting:goroutines/sched/goroutines-created:goroutines/sched/pauses/stopping/other:secondsspanQueue.destroy on non-empty queueuser arena span is on the wrong listruntime: marked free object in span runtime: unblock on closing polldescruntime: inconsistent write deadlineUnable to determine system directoryruntime: VirtualQuery failed; errno=runtime: sudog with non-nil waitlinkruntime: mcall called on m->g0 stackstartm: P required for spinning=true) is not Grunnable or Gscanrunnable
reflect.typeptrdata: unexpected type, reflect: close of receive-only channelreflect: Method on nil interface valuetype conversion error from map to '%v'unsupported type conversion: %v to mapafter decimal point in numeric literalhttp: concurrent read on response bodyfailed to parse Location header %q: %vhttp2: server connection from %v on %phttp: Accept error: %v; retrying in %vScan: unable to scan type %T into UUIDexec: StdoutPipe after process startedexec: StderrPipe after process startedconcurrent map iteration and map writetemplate: %s: executing %q at <%s>: %scan't give argument to non-function %sindirection through explicit nil in %sevalEmptyInterface: nil (can't happen)deepObject parameters must be explodedinvalid function %q: missing overloadsconvert a value to its type identifier[1, 2, 2].exists_one(i, i < 2) // true{'hi': 'you', 'howzit': 'bruv'}.map(k,[5, 10, 15].map(x, x / 5) // [1, 2, 3]deprecated_legacy_json_field_conflictstype mismatch: cannot convert %v to %sno support for message_set_wire_format%v: unable to resolve extension %v: %vfound wrong type: got %v, want messageIPv4 field has octet with leading zerotls: invalid ClientKeyExchange messagetls: invalid ServerKeyExchange messageexpected an Ed25519 public key, got %Tinternal error: unknown signature typetls: server selected unsupported grouptls: unsupported signing key type (%T)tls: early_data without pre_shared_keytls: client sent unexpected early datatls: failed to sign ECDHE parameters: tls: server selected unsupported curvetls: missing ServerKeyExchange messagetls: internal error: unsupported curvemalformed MIME header initial line: %qmime: expected slash after first tokenx509: invalid subject alternative namex509: invalid authority key identifierx509: empty name constraints extensionx509: failed to parse EC private key: x509: cannot validate certificate for Transport is disabled: invalid dsn: %verror while converting to envelope: %vUnexpected status code %d for event %sflag %s set at %s before being definedcrypto/sha256: invalid hash state sizeinsufficient data for base length typeline %d: cannot unmarshal %s%s into %sline %d: field %s not found in type %sdid not find expected <document start>could not find expected directive namefound an incorrect leading UTF-8 octetname reference must be fully qualifiedecdsa: invalid uncompressed public keyecdsa: public key does not match curvechacha20poly1305: ciphertext too largehpke: invalid hybrid KEM secret lengtharch-specific Castagnoli not availableinternal error: unknown string type %dasn1: Unmarshal recipient value is nilcrypto/sha512: invalid hash state sizeinvalid field: no encoder for %v %v %vinvalid octal escape code %q in stringinvalid P224 compressed point encodinginvalid P256 compressed point encodinginvalid P384 compressed point encodinginvalid P521 compressed point encodingbigmod: internal error: bad arithmeticGODEBUG sys/cpu: unknown cpu feature "mlkem: internal error: bitsFilled != 0%s is already set and must be an array.Higgsfield API did not return a job id.At least one --asset value is required.Failed to read Higgsfield API response.https://clerk.higgsfield.ai/oauth/tokenmismatched count during itab table copyout of memory allocating heap arena map/cpu/classes/gc/mark/assist:cpu-seconds/cpu/classes/scavenge/total:cpu-seconds/memory/classes/profiling/buckets:bytesspanQueue.destroy during the mark phasemspan.sweep: bad span state after sweepruntime: blocked write on free polldescPowerRegisterSuspendResumeNotification
cobra_annotation_required_if_others_seterror marshaling 'brand_aesthetics': %w/developer/v2alpha/account/transactionsFailed to start local auth callback at Failed to generate secure random token.OAuth redirect URI must include a port.OAuth redirect URI must include a path.Failed to create temp credentials file. cannot produce iter.Seq2[Value, Value]reflect: OverflowUint of non-uint type reflect.MakeMapWithSize of non-map typeoverload already has a late binding: %stype conversion error from bool to '%v'type conversion error from '%v' to '%v'type conversion error from '%s' to '%s'type conversion error from list to '%v'type conversion error from '%T' to '%v'http2: concurrent read on response bodyhttp: putIdleConn: keep alives disabledusername/password authentication failedUsing sampling decision from parent: %vexec: environment variable contains NULmissing argument to repetition operatortrailing backslash at end of expressioncannot add nil overload to funciton: %sinvalid variable: missing variable nameinvalid function: missing function name"Hello, " + "world!" // "Hello, world!"duration('1h2m3s') // duration('3723s')'hello world'.endsWith('world') // true[1, 2, 3].exists(i, i % 2 != 0) // true[0, -1, 5].exists(num, num < 0) // trueexpression recursion limit exceeded: %dgoogle.golang.org/genproto/protobuf/apigoogle.golang.org/protobuf/types/known/unmarshalScalar: invalid scalar kind %verror in marshaling Any.value field: %vIPv4 field must have at least one digittls: unsupported certificate curve (%s)tls: internal error: wrong nonce lengthno mutually supported protocol versionschain is not signed by an acceptable CAinvalid indexed representation index %dtoo many list-members in baggage-stringx509: invalid subject alternative namesx509: invalid NameConstraints extensionx509: failed to parse URI constraint %qx509: invalid policy mappings extensionx509: unknown EC private key version %d because it doesn't contain any IP SANsx509: signing with MD5 is not supportedbuild line missing '=' after quoted keyextraneous or missing " in quoted-fieldcsv: invalid field or comment delimitermath/big: buffer too small to fit valueRtlDosPathNameToNtPathName_U_WithStatuscannot decode node with unknown kind %dunknown problem generating YAML contentcannot marshal invalid UTF-8 data as %scannot encode node with unknown kind %dfound an incorrect trailing UTF-8 octetdid not find expected hexdecimal numberCould not deserialize ATN with version p.Precpred(p.GetParserRuleContext(), 1)p.Precpred(p.GetParserRuleContext(), 2)p.Precpred(p.GetParserRuleContext(), 3)invalid character %q at start of stringecdsa: unsupported curve by crypto/ecdhecdsa: public key point is the infinityecdsa: private key does not match curvecrypto/rsa: invalid options for Decryptcipher: incorrect tag size given to GCMcrypto/cipher: incorrect GCM nonce sizecrypto/cipher: GCM nonce prefix changedtags don't match (%d vs %+v) %+v %s @%dasn1: Unmarshal recipient value is nil invalid GOAMD64: must be v1, v2, v3, v4fips140: no verification checksum found%v: MessageSet with no extensions fieldinvalid value: merging into nil messageed25519: bad Ed25519ph context length: mlkem: invalid encapsulation key lengthEnhance prompt and generate brand images/developer/v2alpha/images/%s/generationsquality: low, medium, high (default low)Failed to upload game archive (HTTP %d).--start-image accepts only image inputs.Use either --scope or --asset, not both.time: Stop called on uninitialized Timer/linuxbrew/.linuxbrew/Cellar/higgsfield/invalid span in heapArena for user arenabulkBarrierPreWrite: unaligned argumentsruntime: typeBitsBulkBarrier with type  refill of span with free space remaining/cpu/classes/scavenge/assist:cpu-secondsruntime.SetFinalizer: first argument is failed to acquire lock to reset capacitymarkWorkerStop: unknown mark worker modecannot free workbufs when work.full != 0runtime: out of memory: cannot allocate runtime.preemptM: duplicatehandle failedstopTheWorld: broken CPU time accountingglobal runq empty with non-zero runqsizemust be able to track idle limiter eventruntime: SyscallN has too many argumentsgoroutine stack size is not a power of 2address family not supported by protocolerrors: target must be a non-nil pointer13877787807814456755295395851135253906256938893903907228377647697925567626953125https://dev-fnf-api-gw.higgsfield.ai/fnferror reading 'products_or_services': %werror marshaling 'business_overview': %werror marshaling 'detected_language': %werror marshaling 'short_description': %w/developer/v2alpha/audios/%s/generations/developer/v2alpha/videos/%s/generationsMapIter.Key called on exhausted iteratorreflect: FieldByName of non-struct type reflect.Value.Call: call of nil functionreflect.Value.Call: wrong argument countattempted to copy pointer to FP registerreflect.Value.SetBytes of non-byte slicereflect.Value.setRunes of non-rune slicetype conversion error from Bytes to '%v'type conversion not supported for 'type'http2: timeout awaiting response headersFrame accessor called on non-owned Frameinternal error: expecting non-nil streamrequest header %q is not valid in HTTP/2http2: Transport encoding header %q = %qprotocol error: headers after END_STREAMwriteData(stream=%d, p=%d, endStream=%v)host contains '{' (missing initial '/'?)bad wildcard segment (must end with '}')unknown flagNotExistErrorMessageType: %vunsupported optional field selection: %sunsupported optional field selection: %vunexpected Unmarshal for TypeDesc at: %dduration('1ms') < duration('1s') // true'hello world'.endsWith('hello') // falseunsupported comprehension range type: %Tmismatched message type: got %q, want %qfound wrong type: got %v, want extension%v: assigning invalid zero-value messageIPv6 zones cannot be present in a prefixclient doesn't support certificate curveoversized record received with length %dtls: received empty certificates messagetls: client didn't provide a certificatemultipart: unexpected line in Next(): %qmalformed MIME header: missing colon: %qevictOldest(%v) on table with %v entriesx509: malformed extension critical fieldx509: cannot parse IP address of length %s %q is not permitted by any constraintline %d: field %s already set in type %sunsupported flag %q in tag %q of type %scrypto/rsa: input must be hashed messagecrypto/cipher: output smaller than inputcipher: the nonce can't have zero lengthcrypto/cipher: message too large for GCMecdh: private key does not support Bytesquotedprintable: invalid hex byte 0x%02xNumericString contains invalid charactercannot represent time as GeneralizedTimemessage %T is neither a v1 or v2 Messageinvalid type: no encoder for %v %v %v/%vinvalid Unicode escape code %q in stringed25519: bad Ed25519ctx context length: rsa: internal error: inconsistent lengthedwards25519: use of uninitialized Pointunexpected call to os.Exit(0) during testList workspaces available to your accountCEL expression returned %s, expected boolImage generation did not return a job id.voice_change accepts exactly one --video.Model does not accept image media inputs.Failed to decode Higgsfield API response.runtime: pointer to heap type header nil?runtime: typeBitsBulkBarrier without typeWARNING: LIKELY CLEANUP/FINALIZER ISSUES
 branded image generationworkflow <workflow_name> [--param value]...Cannot detect media type from extension %q.https://clerk.higgsfield.ai/oauth/authorizemultiple Read calls return no data or error/memory/classes/metadata/mcache/inuse:bytesruntime.SetFinalizer: first argument is nilruntime.SetFinalizer: finalizer already setgcBgMarkWorker: unexpected gcMarkWorkerModenon in-use span found with specials bit setgrew heap, but no adequate free space foundroot level max pages doesn't fit in summaryruntime.Pinner: argument is not a pointer: runtime: releaseSudog with non-nil gp.paramunknown runnable goroutine during bootstrapruntime: casfrom_Gscanstatus bad oldval gp=runtime:stoplockedm: lockedg (atomicstatus=methodValueCallFrameObjs is not in a modulereset of synctest timer from outside bubblesynctest timer accessed from outside bubbleGcSlice can't handle on-demand gcdata typesinterrupted system call should be restarted    local_nonpersistent_flags+=("--%[1]s")
runtime: waitforsingleobject unexpected; result=CreateWaitableTimerEx when creating timer failedruntime.preemptM: duplicatehandle failed; errno=runtime: malformed profBuf buffer - invalid sizeruntime: taggedPointerPack invalid packing: ptr=attempt to trace invalid or unsupported P statusruntime: waitforsingleobject wait_failed; errno=strconv: illegal AppendFloat/FormatFloat bitSizegroup id '%s' is not defined for subcommand '%s'/developer/v1alpha/marketing-studio/image-stylesOAuth redirect URI must be an http loopback URL.reflect: CallSlice with too many input argumentsinvalid validator: %s unsupported limit type: %vbinary function bound to non-binary overload: %sinvalid UTF-8 in bytes, cannot convert to stringtype registration conflict. found: %v, input: %vnet/http: extended connect not supported by peerinternal error: should have a body in this statenet/http: Hijack called after ServeHTTP finishedDropping transaction: EnableTracing is set to %tThere was an issue when creating the request: %vbufio: writer returned negative count from Writeinvalid string being converted to IP address: %scan't use %v iterate over more than one variableundeclared reference to '%s' (in container '%s')compare two values of the same type for equalitysubtract two numbers, or two time-related valuesmatches('123-456', '^[0-9]+(-[0-9]+)?$') // truetls: CloseWrite called before handshake completeunable to generate random session ticket key: %vfailed to parse certificate #%d in the chain: %wtls: no FIPS compatible certificate chains foundtls: CurvePreferences includes unsupported curvex509: internal error: URI SAN %q failed to parsex509: X25519 key encoded with illegal parametersx509: SAN uniformResourceIdentifier is malformedx509: IP constraint contained value of length %dx509: only RSA, ECDSA and Ed25519 keys supportedInt.GobDecode: encoding version %d not supportedparsing/packing of this type isn't available yetecdsa: curve not supported by ParseRawPrivateKeyout points to big.Int, but defaultValue does notinvalid GOPPC64: must be power8, power9, power10invalid Mutable on field with non-composite typefield %v has invalid type: got %v, want map kindlist field %v cannot be set with read-only valuecrypto/rsa: input must be hashed with given hash  higgsfield marketing-studio brand-kits get <id>voice_change accepts only the --video media flag.slice bounds out of range [::%x] with capacity %yinvalid memory address or nil pointer dereferencepanicwrap: unexpected string after package name: runtime: unexpected waitm - semaphore out of syncs.allocCount != s.nelems && freeIndex == s.nelemsruntime.reflect_makemap: unsupported map key typesweeper left outstanding across sweep generationsfully empty unfreed span set block found in resetcasgstatus: waiting for Gwaiting but is Grunnableinvalid or incomplete multibyte or wide character# bash completion for %-36s -*- shell-script -*-
compare two values of the same type for inequalityduration('1m') - duration('1s') // duration('59s')test whether a string ends with a substring suffix[1, 2, 3, 4].existsOne(num, num % 2 == 0) // falseiteration variable overwrites accumulator variablegoogle.golang.org/genproto/protobuf/source_contextcryptobyte: attempted write while child is pendingtls: received unexpected CertificateStatus messagetls: invalid signature by the server certificate: tls: invalid signature by the client certificate: tls: client offered TLS version older than TLS 1.3x509: missing ASN.1 contents; use ParseCertificatex509: invalid RDNSequence: invalid attribute valuex509: RSA public exponent is not a positive numberx509: internal error: known ExtKeyUsage has no OID^[-+]?[0-9][0-9_]*(?::[0-5]?[0-9])+(?:\.[0-9_]*)?$Precedence predicates are not supported in lexers.crypto/elliptic: nistec rejected normalized scalarcrypto/rsa: prime factors are not relatively primecrypto/cipher: incorrect nonce length given to GCMchacha20: SetCounter attempted to rollback countercrypto/ecdh: public key does not match private keyinvalid Mutable on map with non-message value typefield %v has invalid type: got %v, want slice kindedwards25519: invalid SetUniformBytes input lengthinternal error: too many releases of process handleGetFinalPathNameByHandle returned unexpected path: params\.([A-Za-z_][A-Za-z0-9_]*)\.(all|exists)\s*\(limiterEvent.stop: invalid limiter event type foundpotentially overlapping in-use allocations detectedruntime: netpoll: PostQueuedCompletionStatus failedfatal: systemstack called from unexpected goroutinegodebug: Value of name not listed in godebugs.All: ScanState's Read should not be called. Use ReadRuneOAuth redirect URI must use 127.0.0.1 or localhost.JSON decoder out of sync - data changing underfoot?protocol error: received %T before a SETTINGS framehttp: Transport does not support unencrypted HTTP/2^([[:xdigit:]]{32})-([[:xdigit:]]{16})(?:-([01]))?$Event dropped: telemetry buffer full or unavailableDropped unfinished span: Op=%q TraceID=%s SpanID=%sFailed to build envelope, skipping delivery. %s: %vdefault type does not match variable type: %v != %vcan't use %v to iterate over more than one variablefound no matching overload for '%s' applied to '%s'duration('1m') + duration('1s') // duration('1m1s')[1, 2, 3, 4].exists_one(num, num % 2 == 0) // falseno viable alternative at input '.(true|false|null)'%v: getting mutable reference to non-composite typetls: missing signature_algorithms from TLS 1.2 peertls: VerifyHostname called on TLS server connectiontls: invalid EncryptedClientHelloKey Config KEM: %stls: invalid EncryptedClientHelloKey PrivateKey: %stls: invalid EncryptedClientHelloKey Config KDF: %scrypto/tls: reserved ExportKeyingMaterial label: %stls: server's identity changed during renegotiationtls: server selected unsupported compression formattls: server offered only incompatible point formatstls: server sent an unexpected early_data extensiontls: client did not request an application protocoltls: client offered only incompatible point formatsx509: certificate has expired or is not yet valid: error creating trace metric batch envelope item: %vitem does not implement EnvelopeItemConvertible: %Tfailed to serialize client report: %v, with err: %vline %d: mapping key %#v already defined at line %dcrypto/elliptic: Add was called on an invalid pointinvalid AppendMutable on list with non-message typeinvalid value: setting map field to read-only valueextension %v extends %v outside the extension rangefield %v has invalid type: got %v, want struct kindfield %v has invalid type: %v does not implement %vecdsa: internal error: request size exceeds maximumcrypto/ecdh: internal error: isLess input too largeEnhance marketplace card prompts and generate imagesList image, video, text, and audio generation modelsdeprecated; SDK products list uses cursor paginationupload UUID or local image path (repeatable, 5
span set block with unpopped elements found in resetruntime: GetQueuedCompletionStatusEx failed (errno= runtime: NtCreateWaitCompletionPacket failed; errno=casfrom_Gscanstatus: gp->status is not in scan stateerrors: *target must be interface or implement errorcobra_annotation_bash_completion_filename_extensionsRegisterFlagCompletionFunc: flag '%s' does not exist/developer/v1alpha/marketing-studio/ad-references/%sfield type conversion error for %v.%v value type: %vrequest header "TE" may only be "trailers" in HTTP/2http2: Transport readFrame error on conn %p: (%T) %vprotocol error: received DATA before a HEADERS framebreadcrumb dropped due to BeforeBreadcrumb callback.Event dropped due to transport buffer being full. %swrong number of args for %s: want at least %d got %dwrong number of args for %s: got %d want at least %dinvalid type: type expects 0 or 1 parameters, got %dtest whether a string starts with a substring prefix%v: field descriptor does not belong to this messagetls: invalid EncryptedClientHelloKey Config AEAD: %stls: server selected unsupported protocol version %xtls: received a session ticket with invalid lifetimetls: internal error: session ticket keys unavailabletls: private key type does not match public key typex509: cannot verify signature: insecure algorithm %vConvertSecurityDescriptorToStringSecurityDescriptorWConvertStringSecurityDescriptorToSecurityDescriptorWinternal error: missing handler for resolver table: ecdsa: internal error: unexpectedly masking off bitsprototext: error parsing unknown field wire type: %vreframe accepts at most two --image reference inputs.Media %q is neither a UUID nor an existing file path.Image %q is neither a UUID nor an existing file path.non-concurrent sweep failed to drain all sweep queuesruntime: NtCancelWaitCompletionPacket failed; errno= exited a goroutine internally locked to the OS threadcompileCallback: argument size is larger than uintptrsync/atomic: compare and swap of nil value into ValueOAuth callback listener did not return a TCP address.reflect: non-interface type passed to Type.Implementsreflect.Value.Slice: string slice index out of boundshttp: putIdleConn: too many idle connections for hosthttp2: Framer %p: failed to decode just-written frameillegal use of AllowIllegalReads with ReadMetaHeadershttp2: Transport failed to get client conn for %s: %vnon-CONNECT pattern with unclean path can never matchdescribeConflict called with non-conflicting patternsnet/http: CloseNotify called after ServeHTTP finishedcould not encode event as JSON, skipping delivery: %wDropping transaction: TracesSampler returned rate: %fsmall map with no empty slot (concurrent map writes?)timestamp('2023-07-14T10:30:45.123Z').getMonth() // 6timestamp('2023-01-02T00:00:00Z').getDayOfYear() // 1timestamp('2023-07-14T10:30:45.123Z').getDate() // 14// ensure exactly one key in the map ends in @acme.coinvalid GOLANG_PROTOBUF_REGISTRATION_CONFLICT value: unique.canonMap: ran out of hash bits while iteratingunique.canonMap: ran out of hash bits while insertingtls: unable to generate random session ticket key: %vtls: received unexpected handshake message of type %Ttls: unexpected server_name extension in server hellotls: client does not support uncompressed connectionstls: failed to find any PEM data in certificate inputx509: certificate specifies an incompatible key usagemath/big: internal error: cannot find (D/n) = -1 for ^[-+]?(\.[0-9]+|[0-9]+(\.[0-9]*)?)([eE][-+]?[0-9]+)?$did not find expected alphabetic or numeric characterunexpected character %s, missing ":" after field namecrypto/elliptic: attempted operation on invalid pointcrypto/cipher: counter decreased or remained the samechacha20: internal error: wrong dst and/or src lengthcrypto/ecdh: internal error: mismatched isLess inputsToo many positional args. Use: <%s> [--param value]...draw_to_video accepts exactly one --sketch or --image.Use only one of --sketch or --image for draw_to_video.Model accepts only --image (no roles, no video/audio).Model type %q is not supported by generate create yet.deprecated; not exposed by the current SDK create spechttps://oriented-jay-78.clerk.accounts.dev/oauth/tokenruntime.m memory alignment too small for spinbit mutexmin size of malloc header is not a size class boundarygcControllerState.findRunnable: blackening not enabledno goroutines (main called runtime.Goexit) - deadlock!trace: non-empty full trace buffer for done generationtrace: non-empty full trace buffer for next generation
  higgsfield account transactions --size 50  higgsfield generate create <model> --prompt "..." --image <upload_id>range function recovered a loop body panic and did not resume panickingruntime: GetQueuedCompletionStatusEx returned net_op with invalid key= too many concurrent operations on a single file or socket (max 1048575)if any flags in the group [%v] are set they must all be set; missing %vjson: invalid use of ,string struct tag, trying to unmarshal %q into %vinternal error: attempt to send frame on a half-closed-local stream: %vexec: command with a non-nil Cancel was not created with CommandContexttimestamp('2023-01-01T05:30:00Z').getMonth('America/Los_Angeles') // 11with logical operators being the only operators which can absorb errorstls: peer doesn't support any of the certificate's signature algorithmsdynamic table size update MUST occur at the beginning of a header block^([\x21\x23-\x27\x2A\x2B\x2D\x2E\x30-\x39\x41-\x5a\x5e-\x7a\x7c\x7e]+)$x509: issuer has name constraints but leaf doesn't have a SAN extensioncrypto/ecdsa: use of custom curves is not allowed in FIPS 140-only modeinvalid GOFIPS140: must be off, latest, inprocess, certified, or v1.Y.Z  higgsfield auth login
%[1]sUnsolicited response received on idle HTTP channel starting with %q; err=%vcheck a protocol buffer message for the presence of a field, or check a map// an empty list or map as the range will result in a trivially true resultconsistent with logical operators being the only operators which can absorbexpression. This macro does not short-circuit in order to remain consistent{'a': 'hello', 'aa': 'hellohello'}.existsOne(k, k.startsWith('a')) // falsethe predicate which is equivalent to chaining the filter and three-argumenttls: internal error: attempted to read record with pending application datatls: client sent encrypted_client_hello extension with unsupported versionstls: client sent encrypted_client_hello extension but did not offer TLS 1.3unreachable logic in Decoder.isValueNext, lastToken.kind: %v, openStack: %vruntime.AddCleanup: cleanup function closes over ptr, cleanup will never run  higgsfield generate get <job_id>
  higgsfield generate get <job_id> --json  higgsfield soul-id get <soul_id>
  higgsfield account transactions --size 100 --cursor <cursor>  hf marketplace-cards create --scope full-set --prompt "peach lemonade can" --image product.png--offset is not supported by the current SDK products list spec; use --limit for the first page.overload with late binding cannot be added to function %s: cannot mix late and non-late bindings{'wiley@acme.co': 'coyote', 'aa@milne.co': 'bear'}.exists_one(k, k.endsWith('@acme.co')) // trueb3312fa7e23ee7e4988e056be3f82d19181d9c6efe8141120314088f5013875ac656398d8a2ed19d2a85c8edd3ec2aefaa87ca22be8b05378eb1c71ef320ad746e1d3b628ba79b9859f741e082542a385502f25dbf55296c3a545e3872760ab73617de4a96262c6f5d9e98bf9292dc29f8f41dbd289a147ce9da3113b5f0b8c00a60b1ce1d7e819d7a431d7c90ea0e5fcrypto/rsa: use of hash functions other than SHA-2 or SHA-3 is not allowed in FIPS 140-only mode  higgsfield marketing-studio webproducts create --url https://example.com --title "Landing Page"http: RoundTripper implementation (%T) returned a *Response with content length %d but a nil BodyEvent dropped due to being matched by `IgnoreErrors` option.| Value matched: %s | Filter used: %scrypto/hkdf: use of hash functions other than SHA-2 or SHA-3 is not allowed in FIPS 140-only modecrypto/hmac: use of hash functions other than SHA-2 or SHA-3 is not allowed in FIPS 140-only modeSubmit a high-level intent and a mode; backend assembles a structured prompt and generates images.  higgsfield marketing-studio products list
  higgsfield upload list --video --size 50Secondary and A+ assets need a main image. Include main_image or pass --main-job <completed_job_id>.ed25519: expected opts.Hash zero (unhashed message, for standard Ed25519) or SHA-512 (for Ed25519ph)Image upload %q was not found in recent uploads. Use a local file path or run %s upload list --image.  hf marketplace-cards create --scope product-images --prompt "sparkling lemonade can" --image can.pngcgocheck > 1 mode is no longer supported at runtime. Use GOEXPERIMENT=cgocheck2 at build time instead.http2: failed reading the frame payload: %w, note that the frame header looked like an HTTP/1.1 headerxtg-x-cel-gaulishen-GB-oxendicten-x-i-defaultund-x-i-enochiansee-x-i-mingonan-x-zh-minen-US-u-va-posixList available workspaces, select the active workspace, or return jobs to your private account context.HTTP/1.1 400 Bad Request
  higgsfield workflow get reframe --json  higgsfield marketing-studio dtc-ads generate --prompt "hero shot" --format-id <uuid> --brand-kit-id <uuid>Transaction dropped due to being matched by `IgnoreTransactions` option.| Value matched: %s | Filter used: %sinvalid nil message info; this suggests memory corruption due to a race or shallow copy on the message structinternal/sync.HashTrieMap: ran out of hash bits while inserting (incorrect use of unsafe or cgo, or data race?)Upload local image, video, or audio files and list previously uploaded media IDs for use in generation commands.  higgsfield marketing-studio settings list
  higgsfield voices list --jsoncannot determine upload size: pass a *bytes.Reader, *bytes.Buffer, *strings.Reader, *os.File, or other seekable source (or use UploadFile)  higgsfield generate list
  higgsfield generate list --video --size 50
  higgsfield generate list --text
  higgsfield generate list --jsonCreate custom Soul character references from uploaded images, list existing references, inspect one reference, or wait for training to finish.  higgsfield generate wait <job_id>
  higgsfield generate wait <job_id> --timeout 20m --interval 5s
  higgsfield generate wait <job_id> --quietHTTP/1.1 431 Request Header Fields Too Large
See each sub-command's help for details on how to use the generated script.
  higgsfield generate create <model> --prompt "cinematic product photo" --image <upload_id>  higgsfield marketing-studio brand-kits list
proto3  higgsfield marketing-studio dtc-ads generate --prompt "hero shot" --format-id <uuid>
  higgsfield marketing-studio dtc-ads generate --prompt "..." --format-id <uuid> --brand-kit-id <uuid> --waitCreate marketplace main images, secondary product images, and A+ style modules. Backend keeps marketplace references and prompt templates private, then returns nano_banana_2 prompts for job creation.  higgsfield marketing-studio products create --title "Sneaker" --image <upload_id>
  higgsfield marketing-studio products create --title "Sneaker" --description "Limited release" --image <upload_id>  higgsfield generate create nano_banana_2 --prompt "cinematic product photo" --image ./photo.png
  higgsfield generate create <video_model> --prompt "..." --wait --wait-timeout 20m --wait-interval 5s00010203040506070809101112131415161718192021222324252627282930313233343536373839404142434445464748495051525354555657585960616263646566676869707172737475767778798081828384858687888990919293949596979899^(?:\s*([\x21\x23-\x27\x2A\x2B\x2D\x2E\x30-\x39\x41-\x5a\x5e-\x7a\x7c\x7e]+)\s*|\s*([\x21\x23-\x27\x2A\x2B\x2D\x2E\x30-\x39\x41-\x5a\x5e-\x7a\x7c\x7e]+)\s*=\s*([\x21\x23-\x2b\x2d-\x3a\x3c-\x5B\x5D-\x7e]*)\s*)$  higgsfield marketing-studio products list
The generated definition for this file has moved:
proto3  higgsfield generate cost nano_banana_2 --prompt "cinematic product photo"
  higgsfield generate cost <video_model> --prompt "slow push-in shot" --image ./first.png
  higgsfield generate cost workflow reframe --duration 7.1 --resolution 1080pEstimate credits without creating a job.
For models, params and media flags match generate create. Local file paths are auto-uploaded.
Run `higgsfield model get <job_type>` or `higgsfield workflow get <workflow_name>` to inspect accepted params.  higgsfield generate workflow draw_to_video --video ./source.mp4 --sketch ./frame.png --timestamp 3.2 --prompt "make the jacket red" --wait
  higgsfield generate workflow reframe --video ./source.mp4 --aspect-ratio 9:16 --resolution 720p --wait  higgsfield marketing-studio avatars list
  higgsfield generate create nano_banana_2 --prompt "studio product photo"
  higgsfield generate workflow reframe --video ./source.mp4 --aspect-ratio 9:16
  higgsfield generate cost nano_banana_2 --prompt "studio product photo"
  higgsfield generate wait <job_id>  higgsfield marketing-studio ad-references create --video-input <upload_id>
  higgsfield generate cost workflow <workflow_name> --duration <seconds> --resolution <resolution>
  higgsfield generate cost workflow draw_to_video --duration 8.2 --resolution 720p
  higgsfield generate cost workflow reframe --duration 7.1 --resolution 1080p
  higgsfield generate cost workflow %s --duration <seconds> --resolution <resolution>
  higgsfield generate cost workflow %s --duration 8.2 --resolution 720p
  higgsfield generate workflow voice-change --video <id|path> --voice-id <id> [flags]
  higgsfield generate workflow voice-change --video ./clip.mp4 --voice-id 9f8b... --voice-type element --wait
  higgsfield generate workflow dubbing --video <id|path> --target-language <code> [flags]
  higgsfield generate workflow dubbing --video ./clip.mp4 --target-language spa --wait
  higgsfield generate workflow draw_to_video --video <id|path> --sketch <id|path> --timestamp <seconds> --prompt <text> [flags]
  higgsfield generate workflow draw_to_video --video ./source.mp4 --sketch ./frame.png --timestamp 3.2 --prompt "make the jacket red" --wait
  higgsfield generate workflow reframe --video <id|path> --aspect-ratio <ratio> [flags]
  higgsfield generate workflow reframe --video ./source.mp4 --aspect-ratio 9:16 --resolution 720p --wait
  higgsfield generate workflow reframe --video ./source.mp4 --aspect-ratio 16:9 --mode pro --image ./ref.png
java_generate_equals_and_hash
https://fnf-api-gw.higgsfield.ai/fnf
i-klingon
-ldflags="-s -w -X main.version=1.0.2 -X main.commit=22472d4edbe753c6076ca4ac07956721096ec4b2 -X main.date=2026-06-30T09:10:17Z -X main.sentryDSN=https://a2b7b7f76f4f321559ccf72c2b8c9ec7@o4509169762697216.ingest.de.sentry.io/4511332137566288 -X github.com/higgsfield-ai/cli-src/internal/config.buildDefaultAPIURL=https://fnf-api-gw.higgsfield.ai/fnf -X github.com/higgsfield-ai/cli-src/internal/config.buildConfigLocked=true"
crypto/des.(*desCipher).generateSubkeys
crypto/tls.generateOuterECHExt
crypto/tls.generateOuterECHExt.func2
crypto/tls.generateOuterECHExt.func1
crypto/tls.rsaKeyAgreement.generateServerKeyExchange
crypto/tls.rsaKeyAgreement.generateClientKeyExchange
crypto/tls.(*ecdheKeyAgreement).generateServerKeyExchange
crypto/tls.(*ecdheKeyAgreement).generateClientKeyExchange
crypto/tls.generateECDHEKey
crypto/tls.(*rsaKeyAgreement).generateClientKeyExchange
crypto/tls.(*rsaKeyAgreement).generateServerKeyExchange
compress/flate.generateFixedOffsetEncoding
compress/flate.generateFixedLiteralEncoding
compress/flate.(*huffmanEncoder).generate
github.com/antlr4-go/antlr/v4.(*ATNDeserializer).generateRuleBypassTransitions
github.com/antlr4-go/antlr/v4.(*ATNDeserializer).generateRuleBypassTransition
crypto/internal/fips140/mlkem.generateKey1024
crypto/internal/fips140/mlkem.generateKey1024.func1
crypto/internal/fips140/mlkem.generateKey
crypto/internal/fips140/mlkem.generateKey.func1
<autogenerated>
/home/runner/work/cli-src/cli-src/internal/cmd/generate.go
-ldflags="-s -w -X main.version=1.0.2 -X main.commit=22472d4edbe753c6076ca4ac07956721096ec4b2 -X main.date=2026-06-30T09:10:17Z -X main.sentryDSN=https://a2b7b7f76f4f321559ccf72c2b8c9ec7@o4509169762697216.ingest.de.sentry.io/4511332137566288 -X github.com/higgsfield-ai/cli-src/internal/config.buildDefaultAPIURL=https://fnf-api-gw.higgsfield.ai/fnf -X github.com/higgsfield-ai/cli-src/internal/config.buildConfigLocked=true"
